<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on biggins</title>
    <link>https://www.biggins.tech/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on biggins</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 01:43:36 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.biggins.tech/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Party School</title>
      <link>https://www.biggins.tech/post/party_school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 01:43:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biggins.tech/post/party_school/</guid>
      <description>Thursday comes, barely half way through the week
Time for ever’one run to grab drink
Tomorrows Friday, it ain’t the end of the week
It doesn’t matter nobody want sit and think
It makes me sad sometimes
we forget the blessing it is to feel
it makes me sad sometimes
no one wants to be real
Saturday will come
And the drinking will start early
Grab a drink “don’t be dumb”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lonesome Soliloquy: The Fiction of Negative Numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.biggins.tech/post/the-fiction-of-negative-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:19:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biggins.tech/post/the-fiction-of-negative-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Now, I know, the title The Fiction of Negative Numbers is bold at best, and undermines my credibility at worst. In an effort to avoid the worst-case, I feel it&amp;rsquo;s important to establish my ethos, or lack there of.
I&amp;rsquo;m by no means a mathematician, far from it. I neither have an advanced degree in mathematics, nor physics, or any other mathematics intensive field. I have not been enrolled in a mathematics course, regardless of discipline, in north of 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lonesome Soliloquy: The Preamble</title>
      <link>https://www.biggins.tech/post/the_lonesome_soliloquy_v0-the-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 02:55:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biggins.tech/post/the_lonesome_soliloquy_v0-the-intro/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, to the inagural iteration of The Lonesome Soliloquy Series. For many, and, I surmise for all initially, me included, will find the topics, notions, ideas, opinions&amp;ndash;whatever adjective one may choose&amp;ndash;far too incongruent to justify them belonging to a singular literary entity, a Series, for lack of a better word. And, from this perspective, I cannot disagree.
This is not a series of a subject matter; this is a series of thought, of thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Your Heart Breaks</title>
      <link>https://www.biggins.tech/post/when-your-heart-breaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 23:48:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biggins.tech/post/when-your-heart-breaks/</guid>
      <description>What a peculiar time&amp;ndash;when your heart breaks&amp;ndash;that is, extraordinary even. Such a state, the state of a shattered heart, a state where there exists little room for brevity in describing.
The wise words of my dear friend Aeschylus:
“Even in our sleep, pain which cannot forget falls drop by drop upon the heart, until, in our own despair, against our will, comes wisdom through the awful grace of God.”
It&amp;rsquo;s an affliction of the heart, a afflication I presently bear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ode to Silence</title>
      <link>https://www.biggins.tech/post/ode-to-silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 19:40:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biggins.tech/post/ode-to-silence/</guid>
      <description>Ode To Silence Throughout the land, all was quiet, silence, was all to see.
The world held still; was this all there is to be?
There was no war, and no epidemic plagued her people
But the music had died; even the church bells of the steeple
What was this demon, who had robbed the world of joy?
Surely, a very cunning, evil thing could devise such a ploy
But, instead, in the heart lied this oppressor</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
